A Guide to the University of Virginia, Vice-President for Student Affairs, Office Administrative Files
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia, Vice-President for Student Affairs, Office Administrative Files
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-18/1/1.791
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Scope and Content
Office administrative files of the Vice-President for Student Affairs, University of Virginia.
Contents List
- Series I: General Correspondence
  - Athletics: Blackburn 1970 January- 1971 February (Folder 1)
  - Rapier Magazine, 1968 November- 1970 June, n.d. (Folder 1)
  - Stone Commission, 1972 September- December (Folder 1)
  - Virginia Spectator, 1969 July- 1970 March (Folder 1)
- Series II: Budget
  - General Financial Correspondence, 1971 August- 1973 December (Folder 1)
  - Biennial Budget, 1971 (Folder 1)
  - Equipment and Travel Requests, 1974 January- 1977 March (Folder 1)
  - State Budget, 1973 December- 1975 February (Folder 1)
  - Vice- President for Business and Finance, 1971 June- 1974 April (Folder 1)
- Series III: Scholarships
  - Aunspaugh Scholarship, 1971 June- July (Folder 1)
  - Latimer Scholarship, 1966 September- 1970 November (Folder 1)
  - Mason Memorial Scholarship, 1972 January- 1975 March (Folder 1)
  - Thomas Scholarship, 1963 March- 1972 May, n.d. (Folder 1)
  - Wagenheim Memorial Fellowship, 1965 November- 1968 June (Folder 1)
  - Whitehead Foundation, 1972 November- 1978 March (Folder 1)
- Series IV: Scholarships (Restricted)
  - Adger Scholarships: Correspondence, 1965 September- 1974 October (Folder 2)
  - Adger Scholarships: Applications and Related Correspondence, 1973 (Folder 2)
  - Gooch Scholarship, 1970 November- 1975 April (Folder 2)
  - Lefevre Awards, 1962 September- 1967 May (Folder 2)
- Series V: Search Committees (Restricted)
  - Dean of Admissions Search Committee, 1975 (Folder 2)
  - African American Affairs Search Committee, 1975 November- 1976 June, n.d. (Folder 2)
  - Student Health Screening Committee, 1978 (Folder 2)